(Sheldon:)Oh, my.
- Back off, Sheldon.
- What?
(Raj:)If you do not stop hitting on my lady,
you will feel the full extent of my wrath.
(Sheldon:)I'm not hitting on her.
(Lalita:)And I am not your lady.
(Howard:)And you have no wrath.
(Raj:)You are my lady. Our parents said so.
We are, for all purposes,
100 percent hooked up.
(Lalita:)Let's get something straight.
(Lalita:)The only reason I came tonight
was to get my parents off my case.
I don't need to be getting
this old-world crap from you.
That's the kind of spirit with which Princess
Panchali led the monkeys to freedom.
- Screw Panchali.
- You can't talk to me like that.
But you're not Princess Panchali.
(Sheldon:)Luckily for you.
She could have you beheaded.
- Sheldon, are you hungry?
- I could eat.
(Lalita:)Let's go.
(Raj:)What just happened?
(Leonard:)Beats the hell out of me.
I'll tell you what happened. I just
learned how to pick up Indian chicks.